<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Lanlan</title>
    <link>https://glanfaloth.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Lanlan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://glanfaloth.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jurors or Murderers? A Paradox of Justice</title>
      <link>https://glanfaloth.github.io/posts/jurors-or-murderers-a-paradox-of-justice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://glanfaloth.github.io/posts/jurors-or-murderers-a-paradox-of-justice/</guid>
      <description>Book Review: Murder on the Orient Express SPOILER ALERT! The book review may reveal key plots
Famed crime novelist Agatha Christie published the classic Murder on the Orient Express in 1934. It is set on the Orient express on its journey from Vienna to Istanbul.
One day, a passenger is found dead, stabbed 12 times. The train is stalled by heavy snowdrift, and the renowned Belgian detective Hercule Poirot&amp;rsquo;s trip is interrupted to investigate the case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Door and Road of Socialism - The Epic Meeting of Honecker and Mao</title>
      <link>https://glanfaloth.github.io/posts/door-and-road-of-socialism-the-epic-meeting-of-honecker-and-mao/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://glanfaloth.github.io/posts/door-and-road-of-socialism-the-epic-meeting-of-honecker-and-mao/</guid>
      <description>course thesis: introduction to Mao Zedong thoughts and theoretical system of socialism with Chinese characteristic This fiction does not represent the author political position.
 To my mind, the so-called “socialist society” is not anything immutable. Like all other social formations, it should be conceived in a state of constant flux and change. ——Friedrich Engels
 On October 29, 1976, the General Secretary of the Socialist Unity Party of Germany, Erich Honecker, was elected chairman of the Council of State of German Democratic Republic.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>